梅達把她的手指...
Mayda slides her fingers in...
一直伸進她的婚戒里
all the way up to her... her wedding ring.
她把你推倒  然后傾下身來
She pushes you onto your back and leans down.
把手指伸進你嘴里  讓你嘗到
Puts the fingers into your mouth so you can... taste them.
戒指的金味兒
The gold of the ring...
你的舌尖可以嘗到金屬的腥味兒
You could taste the sting of the metal on your tongue...
混合著她的屄味兒
mixed with the taste of her cunt.
她傾下身來  沖你的耳朵低語
She leans down, whispers in your ear,
"我愛你  加吉克
"I love you, Gagik.
我愛你"
I love you."
-我就要來了  -她跨著你  把你拉進體內
- I'm close, man. - She straddles you, pulls you inside...
她的臀部前后摩挲  來回摩擦
grinds her hips back and forth, back and forth--
該死  你真會說
Ah, damn, you're good with words.
人人影視傾情奉獻
翻譯  草草
時間軸  小式
顧問  老杜
后期  餓得慌
校對  草草
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第四季  第一集
"...新罕布什爾兩百年來
"...New Hampshire for over 200 years.
一直有些起起落落
There've been ups and downs along the way.
就像大埃默斯基格"
Like the big A-mos-ke-ag."
埃默  埃默斯
Am... Amos--
聯系到她了嗎
Do you have her?
她不肯接電話
She won't get on the phone.
-那就打給她的保安  -我打了
- Then get her detail on the phone. - I did.
他們不能逼她跟您說話  先生
They can't force her to talk to you, sir.
我們得考慮我單獨出席活動  她不在身邊時
We need to think about what to say when I show up at this event
該說什么
and she's not with me.
我不想讀錯詞  讓情況更糟
And I don't want to make it worse by mispronouncing this.
這個詞怎么讀
How do you say this word?
他們怎么不給講話注音
They didn't put in the goddamn phonetics in this speech!
又不能讓我自己去查
And I can't be expected to look this shit up myself!
我去替您查  先生
I'll find out for you, sir.
當然  這些年來...
And of course, there's been...
"一直有些起起落落"
"...ups and downs along the way."
就像20年代為薪酬和工時而舉行的
Like the big Amoskeag strike in the 1920s
大埃默斯基格罷工
over pay and hours.
但這個行業也還是挺過來了
But this industry survived that as well.
這間屋子里的每個人都在傳承一個傳統
And all of you in this room have been carrying on a tradition
始于國家創始之初的傳統
that goes back to the beginning of this country,
你們應該為此感到萬分驕傲
and that's something you have to be very, very proud of!
"但這個州還有一項傳統
"But there's another tradition in this state:
不自由毋寧死
Live Free or Die.
我妻子..."
Now, my wife--"
這個州還有一項傳統
There's another tradition in this state:
不自由毋寧死
Live Free or Die.
當然  你們中一些人可能在報紙上讀到了
Now, of course, as some of you may read in the papers,
也聽到電視上的權威人士說了
and, uh, hear from the television pundits
我的對手在新罕布什爾有10個百分點的領先
that my opponent has a ten-point lead here in New Hampshire.
但是
But...
你們不能讓民調和權威人士指揮你們
you're not gonna let polls and pundits tell you what to do.
-不  -或是告訴你們選舉日該怎么投票
- No! - Or tell you how to vote on Election Day.
你們要讓他們知道新罕布什爾人民能自己做主
You are gonna show them that New Hampshire makes up its own mind.
桶匠行業歡迎安德伍德總統
謝謝  謝謝大家今天前來
Thank you! Thank you all for coming out today.
天佑美國  謝謝
And God bless America. Thank you.
安德伍德  安德伍德
Underwood! Underwood! Underwood!
謝謝  非常感謝  謝謝
Thank you very much. Thank you. Thank you.
謝謝大家  非常感謝
Thank you all. Thank you all very much.
謝謝
Thank you.
她10分鐘前在達拉斯降落了
She landed in Dallas ten minutes ago.
我們的說法是她去為初選打基礎了
Our story is she's down there laying groundwork for the primary.
這只能給我們一兩天時間
That only gives us a day or two.
如果她不參加活動  他們會覺得我有所隱瞞
If she's not doing events, they'll think we're hiding something.
你覺得她會待在農場嗎
You think she'll stay put on the ranch?
我不知道  你盯住她一切活動
I have no idea. You keep track of all of her movements.
訪客  是誰  次數
Visitors, names, times,
他們拉的屎什么顏色  臭不臭
the color of their shit and how much it stinks.
-是  先生  -你這就上飛機
- Yes, sir. - And I want you on a plane.
-回華盛頓嗎  -去德克薩斯州
- Back to Washington? - Down to Texas.
-她在哪  -主臥
- Where is she? - The master bedroom.
黑爾太太提到她可能要打個盹
Mrs. Hale mentioned that she might take a nap.
我的房間布置好了嗎
Is my room made up?
正在撣塵
It's being dusted right now.
-我想看看  -是  女士
- I'd like to take a look. - Yes, ma'am.
德州很重要
Well, Texas is an important state.
獲得提名我們需要10%的代表
Nearly 10% of the delegates we need for the nomination.
但您說第一夫人今天會陪您一起來的
But you said the First Lady would be here with you today.
是啊  今早我們考慮了一下
Yes, well, when we assessed things this morning,
對新罕布什爾很有信心
we felt good about New Hampshire.
看看這群人  看他們多熱情
I mean, look at this crowd, the enthusiasm.
你好  你好  我的老天
Hello, hello. Oh, my goodness.
你好  你真是可愛  叫什么名字
Hello there, aren't you a cutie? What's your name?
-蓋比  -你好  蓋比
- Gabby. - Hello, Gabby.
總之  我們想計劃未來
Anyway, we wanted to start looking ahead.
克萊爾就是德州人
Claire's from Texas,
所以她提前過去也是應該的
so it made sense for her to head down there early.
你好  你好  謝謝你們前來
Hello. Hello. Thank you for coming out.
你不告訴我情況我就沒法做工作
I can't do my job if you keep me in the dark.
你只需要知道你要往聲明里寫的內容
All you need to know is what you put out in the statement.
-是吵架了嗎  -賽斯
- Was it an argument? - Seth.
聽著  我每天忙著競選的各種事
Look, I'm working 20 hours a day here on a normal day
就要干20個小時了  現在還要應付這個
with the campaign in full swing, and now this is on my plate?
我可以控制損害
Look, I can do damage control,
但我得知道損害是什么
but I have to know what the damage is.
好吧  我告訴你  我先去我房間
Okay. I'll fill you in. Let me get up to my room.
歡迎來達拉斯
Welcome to Dallas.
或許是個誘餌
Or maybe it's a decoy,
想騙我們在德州買廣告
trying to lure us into making ad-buys in Texas.
那就能解釋這為什么沒寫進她的日程了
That would explain why it wasn't announce as part of her schedule.
你跟我們在達拉斯的朋友通過話了嗎
Have you spoken to our friends in Dallas?
沒見人  沒打電話
No meetings or calls.
如果她有活動  我們會知道的
If she were making the rounds, we'd know.
他們要么是很會掩蓋
Well, they're either excellent at covering their tracks,
要么就是出事了
or something's up.
-什么事  -不知道  但我想知道
- Like what? - I don't know, but I wanna find out.
梅達
亞美尼亞驕傲
她要離開我  她懷著我的孩子呢
She's gonna fucking leave me. My kid in her belly.
她卻要假裝我根本不存在
And she gonna act like I never existed.
大概都把婚戒給當掉了
Probably pawned the wedding ring already.
-多少了  -還差兩個
- How many is that? - Two more.
-你能怪她嗎  -能  我能
- Can you blame her, though? - Yeah, I can blame her.
我給了她一切  她要奪走我的孩子
I gave her everything. She gonna rob me of my kid?
他上高中時  你還出不去呢
He's gonna be in high school before you're out.
那我也還是他父親
I'll still be his fucking father.
你得讓他們向前看
You gotta let them move on, man.
-否則不公平  -我告訴你什么不公平
- It's unfair not to. - Let me tell you about unfair.
好嗎  我進來就不公平
Okay? Unfair is I'm even in here,
那賤婊子都不知道
and that fucking bitch doesn't even know it.
她以為我活該進來
She thinks I belong in this shithole?
你殺了人啊
You did kill a guy.
-你是說你沒殺嗎  -我沒那么說
- Are you saying you didn't? - I didn't say shit.
因為我
Because I...
我有過懷疑
I had my doubts.
什么意思
What do you mean your doubts?
就是
Just...
從沒覺得你是個殺人犯  僅此而已
never struck me as a killer, that's all.
你不了解我
You don't know what I am!
拜托
Come on!
放開  我無法呼吸了
Let up! I can't breathe.
我只是說
All I'm saying is...
我做犯罪新聞的時候
I interviewed a lot of murder suspects
采訪過很多殺人嫌犯
when I was on the crime beat.
我覺得你是無辜的
I think you're innocent.
我覺得你沒殺人
I think you didn't do it.
那些人  他們會活剝了你
These guys, they'll skin you alive.
還逼著你對著鏡子看著他們那么做
Make you watch in a mirror while they do it.
什么人
What guys?
聽說過洛杉磯的亞美尼亞幫嗎
You ever hear of Armenian Power in LA?
-沒有  -他們的頭號人物
- No. - Their top guy.
那混蛋肯定不會進監獄啊
No way that motherfucker was going to jail, huh?
我沒有選擇
I didn't have a choice.
那么你沒做嘍
So, you didn't do it?
我做了什么沒做什么無所謂
It doesn't matter what I did or what I didn't do.
重要的是我說我做了什么
It matters what I said I did.
你是為誰背鍋
Who did you take the fall for?
《華爾街電訊報》的一項全國民調顯示
A national Wall Street Telegraph poll finds
康威州長在共和黨競選中處于領先
Governor Conway leading the Republican field
48%的共和黨初選選民表示他是他們的首選
with 48% of GOP primary voters saying he's their first choice,
超過其他候選人20%
over 20% more than any other candidate.
康威自2015年5月
Conway has had a dramatic ascent
宣布參選后支持率就扶搖直上
since he announced his candidacy in May of 2015.
康威領跑
當時《華爾街電訊報》的另一項民調顯示
In another Wall Street Telegraph poll conducted at the time,
他只俘獲了18%的共和黨初選選民
he only captured 18% of GOP primary voters.
很多人認為他的年輕和缺乏...
Many felt that his young age and his lack of...
密查姆
Meechum!
-是  先生  -克萊爾的衣服也在這里
- Yes, sir? - Claire's clothes are here.
我去叫先遣的人
I'll get Advance.
以及他競選對
Along with his campaign's focus
他成功的紐約州州長任期的強調
on his successful tenure as Governor of New York,
他的服役記錄...
his service in the Air...
抱歉  先生
My apologies, sir.
她的衣服是昨晚運來的  我們忘記做調整了
Her wardrobe shipped last night and we neglected to adjust.
-好吧  拿出去就是了  -是  先生
- All right, just get it out. - Yes, sir.
他在愛荷華州的每場活動
Hundreds of supporters lined up
都有上百名支持者排隊等候
at nearly every one of his Iowa events,
有時甚至是上千人
sometimes numbering in the thousands.
人群里格外突出的是退伍軍人
Prominent in the crowd were military veterans.
康威的祖父是海軍一級準將
Conway's grandfather was a Navy chief warrant officer
曾在二戰中在太平洋戰場作戰
who fought in the Pacific theater of World War II.
-康威的表現被與...  -密查姆
- Conway's approach has been likened... - Meechum.
1960年的約翰·F·肯尼迪總統競選相提并論
...to that of John F. Kennedy's 1960 presidential campaign.
既有公共場合的魅力  又有私下里的從容
A combination of public charm and personal poise.
上周  在一個競選活動上...
Last week, at a campaign event...
今早你去她房間里時
This morning when you went into her room...
我告訴她我們就要出發了
Uh, I told her we were leaving soon.
她...
She just...
她在看一張照片
She was looking at a photograph...
是您給她的那個曼荼羅
of the mandala, the one you gave her.
...曼徹斯特的活動  但第一夫人不在身側
...event in Manchester, but without the First Lady.
-安德伍德政府的聲明  -晚安  先生
- Reports from the Underwood administration... - Good night, sir.
表示克萊爾·安德伍德
...have stated that Claire Underwood...
-陪我一會兒  -先生
- Keep me company for a bit. - Sir?
坐吧  我得看會兒東西
You just have a seat. I've got some reading that I have to do.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
但您說第一夫人今天會陪您一起來的
But you said the First Lady would be here with you today.
是啊  今早我們考慮了一下
Yes, well, when we assessed things this morning,
對新罕布什爾很有信心
we felt good about New Hampshire.
看看這群人  看他們多熱情
I mean, look at this crowd, the enthusiasm.
你好  你好  我的老天
Hello, hello. Oh, my goodness.
你好  你真是可愛  叫什么名字
Hello there, aren't you a cutie? What's your name?
-蓋比  -你好  蓋比
- Gabby. - Hello, Gabby.
把那關掉
Turn that off.
克萊爾就是德州人
Claire's from Texas,
所以她提前過去也是應該的
so it made sense for her to head down there early.
你好  你好  謝謝你們前來
Hello. Hello. Thank you for coming out.
"你真是可愛"
"Hmm, aren't you a cutie?"
-你干什么  -您睡著了  先生
- What are you doing? - You fell asleep, sir.
您的眼鏡  我...
Your glasses, I was...
對不起  先生  我不是有意...
I'm sorry, sir. I didn't mean to...
-您沒事吧  先生  -有事
- You all right, sir? - No.
我是說  沒事  我就是...
I mean, yes. I'm just...
-您需要點什么嗎  水  -不用
- Can I get you anything? Some water? - I'm fine.
很晚了  你該睡會兒了
It's late. You should get some sleep.
如果您需要我就留下
I'll stay if you like.
我想一個人待著  不過謝謝你了
I think I'd like to be alone, but thank you.
好的  先生
Of course, sir.
請小心腳下
Watch your step, please.
-莉安  -安德伍德夫人
- LeAnn. - Mrs. Underwood.
-我們去散個步吧  -好
- Let's take a walk. - Of course.
你讓一個紅[共和黨]州又關心起了民主黨
You've made the Democrats relevant again in a very red state.
你要我為德州的活動助勢嗎
You want me to help ramp up the Texas operation?
不  我不是為初選而來的
No, I'm not here for the primary.
我想競選30選區議員
I'm here to run for the 30th,
我希望你做我的競選經理
and I want you to run my campaign.
白宮說你是來...
The White House is saying that you're here to--
那只是為了不讓國會競選吸引太多注意
That's just so we don't draw attention to the congressional race.
桃瑞絲·瓊斯  她女兒要競選
Doris Jones, her daughter's running.
得說服那位女議員
The congresswoman would need to be convinced.
你是說西莉婭會退出
You're saying Celia bows out?
她等  兩年后  席位就是她的
She waits. In two years, the seat is hers.
至多四年
Four at the most.
-參議員嗎  -或許
- Senate? - Possibly.
或者州長  2020年
Or governor, 2020.
總統也同意嗎
And the president's on board with this?
完全同意
Completely.
聽著  就算你能說服西莉婭
Look, even if you could convince Celia,
那也還有個大問題
there's still a big problem.
-我是白人  -白得徹頭徹尾
- That I'm white. - Lily white.
穿著設計師鞋  量體剪裁的衣服
In your designer heels and tailored dresses, I mean...
看看這片地產  安德伍德夫人
look at this property, Mrs. Underwood.
一個跟金博士一起游行的女人
A woman who marched with Dr. King
不會有耐心應付一個...
is not gonna have much patience for...
什么
For what?
外人
An outsider.
我認為我們可以改變她對我的看法
Well, I believe we can change her opinion of me.
聽著  我不介意迎難而上
Look, I don't mind betting against the odds.
否則  我也不會在德州為民主黨做顧問了
If I did, I wouldn't be consulting for Democrats in Texas.
-但你所要求的  -你創辦你公司時  莉安
- But what you're asking me-- - When you started your firm, LeAnn,
你父親跟我父親說你是在犯下大錯誤
your father told mine that you were making a huge mistake.
那是因為他是個共和黨人
That's because he was a Republican.
是啊  但你沒有犯錯  不是嗎
Yes, but you didn't make a mistake, did you?
你證明他錯了
You proved him wrong.
很多顧問都能告訴我這為什么不行
Now, a dozen consultants can tell me why this won't work,
但我覺得你能告訴我這為什么行
but I think you can tell me why it can.
密查姆說她進去了一個多小時
Meechum said she was in there for over an hour.
哈維不是我們的人
We don't own Harvey.
沃恩認為她在等鄧巴
Vaughn thinks she's been holding out for Dunbar.
她不會是為初選跟她見面
She wouldn't be meeting with her about the primary.
或許她覺得她可以競選什么
Maybe she thinks she can run for something.
-什么  這輪嗎  -她一直希望當選公職
- What? This cycle? - Elected office has always been her goal.
現在沒有缺職
There aren't any open races.
在德州沒有  只有桃瑞絲·瓊斯
Not in Texas. Except for Doris Jones.
嗯  但她女兒打算競選那個職位
Yeah, but her daughter's running for that seat.
她還沒宣布呢
She hasn't announced yet.
這就給了克萊爾機會
Which gives Claire an opening.
誰啊
Hello?
-誰啊  -莉安
- Hello? - LeAnn?
道格·斯坦普
Doug Stamper.
我還以為我走錯了...
Wasn't sure if I was in the right--
德州就這么打招呼嗎
Is that how you say hi in Texas?
抱歉  電梯周末一般是停用的
Sorry, the elevators are usually locked down on the weekends.
我們樓里進過盜竊犯
We've had some burglaries in the building.
-認識你很高興  道格  -幸會
- It's nice to meet you, Doug. - Pleasure.
安德伍德夫人沒告訴我你來這兒了
Mrs. Underwood didn't tell me you were in town.
我剛到  總統覺得我該來
I just got in. President thought it'd be a good idea
協助競選事宜
if I were here to help coordinate on the campaign.
我還沒正式加入呢
Well, I'm not officially on board yet.
我想看看明天會面的結果
I wanted to see how the meeting goes tomorrow.
會面
The meeting?
桃瑞絲·瓊斯  第一夫人沒告訴你嗎
Doris Jones. The First Lady didn't tell you?
沒有
No.
失陪一下
Will you excuse me for a moment?
-我去打個電話  -好的
- I just have to make a quick call. - Of course.
是總統
It's the president.
喂
Hello?
道格說你拿著槍出來迎他
Doug tells me you greeted him with a firearm.
嗯  我們遇到了些問題...
Yeah, we've been having some issues with--
你知道槍哪點讓我著迷嗎  莉安
Do you know what fascinates me about guns, LeAnn?
扣下扳機  砰
You pull a trigger and bang,
一顆子彈噴出  快過聲速
a bullet explodes out faster than the speed of sound.
如果你站的不是地方
And if you're on the wrong end of that bullet,
你還沒聽到聲就會被它擊中
why, it hits you before you even hear it.
總統先生  請原諒  但是
Mr. President, forgive me, but--
不  你聽著  莉安
No, I want you to hear me, LeAnn.
你要停下跟克萊爾的胡鬧
You will walk away from this nonsense with Claire.
你不要打電話  也不要接電話
You will not make a phone call nor answer one.
不要解釋
You will offer no explanation.
不管你跟我妻子談了什么
Whatever you discussed with my wife,
你要全部忘記  永遠不再提及
you will erase it from your mind and never speak of it again.
告訴我你聽到了
Tell me I've been heard.
是的  我聽到了
Yes, I heard you.
很好
Good.
真可愛
This is cute.
請把它放下
Put it down, please.
當紀念品了
Souvenir.
電話也給我吧
I'll take that phone, too.
今晚愉快
Have a good night.
多快
How soon?
法官正在審核減刑令
The judge is reviewing the Rule 35 order now.
他一簽字  他們逮捕了人
I mean, once he signs it, if they make an arrest,
這些人很快就能想明白
it won't take these guys long to figure out
是我跟聯調局告密了
it was me that talked to the Feds.
他一簽字  那就是幾小時  而不是幾天的事
Well, once he signs, it'll be a matter of hours, not days.
證人保護計劃的安排已經定好了
The WITSEC arrangements are already being made.
-你知道他們要送我去哪嗎  -不
- You know where they're sending me? - Nope.
我不會知道的  沒人會知道
And I never will. Nobody will.
除了司法部
Except for the DOJ.
如果你有事要找我
If you need to reach me for anything,
你得通過證人保護計劃負責人聯系我
you're gonna have to contact me through the WITSEC officer.
我怕的不僅是亞美尼亞人
It's not just the Armenians I'm afraid of.
-盧卡斯  -我知道你一直不信
- Lucas... - I know you never believed me
-我說的總統的那些事  -聽著  聽好
- about the president but-- - Look. Listen carefully.
美國政府現在不是你的敵人了
The U.S. Government is not your enemy now.
好嗎  他們在保護你
Okay? They're protecting you.
他就是政府
He is the government.
連白宮都不知道誰能靠減刑規則獲釋
Not even the White House knows who gets released on Rule 35.
除非司法部長說出去
Unless the Attorney General tells them,
幾乎從來沒有那種事
which almost never happens.
聽著
Listen.
你干得很不錯  盧卡斯
You did good work here, Lucas.
你要出去了
You're getting out.
開心點吧
Try to be happy about that.
你就這么放松嗎
This how you unwind?
我從沒來過這里
I've never been here in my life.
我想找個不會被認出來的地方
I wanted some place we wouldn't be recognized.
擺球吧
Rack 'em up.
-你說你有東西給我  -是的
- You said you had something to offer. - Yes.
保險
Insurance.
我們拿下了愛荷華州
We took Iowa.
在新罕布什爾州也追上來了
We're closing the gap in New Hampshire.
你們在愛荷華州是勉強勝出
You squeaked by in Iowa.
周二之前你在新罕布什爾是追不上差距的
You're not gonna close the gap in New Hampshire by Tuesday.
-你自信過頭了  -你還是新聞發言人呢
- You're overconfident. - And you're still Press Secretary.
他可沒讓你做幕僚長
He didn't make you Chief of Staff.
別告訴我你沒想往那兒鉆
Don't tell me you weren't angling for it.
你想要什么
What's your ask?
一件我們可用的事
One solid thing for us to work with.
如果打擊了他  你就有安全墊了
It tanks him, you got a cushion.
如果沒用
It doesn't?
你還能繼續在白宮工作
You still have your job in the White House.
我憑什么信你
Why should I trust you?
如果你輸了  不想有個后備計劃嗎
Wouldn't you rather have a back-up plan in your pocket if you lose?
該你了
Your shot.
我們保證給你在政府留個位置
We guarantee you a place in our administration
我做兩年的幕僚長
after my two years as Chief of Staff.
然后就是你
Then it's you.
告訴我德州是怎么回事
Tell me what's happening in Texas.
-安德伍德夫人  -議員女士  見到你真高興
- Mrs. Underwood. - Congresswoman, so good to see you.
我也很高興  請進吧
Wonderful to see you, too. Please, come in.
西莉婭  見到你也很高興
Celia, so good to see you, too.
很高興  安德伍德夫人
Always a pleasure, Mrs. Underwood.
莉安早先給我打電話  說她來不了了
LeAnn called me a little while ago. Said she couldn't make it.
議員女士  我叫莉安安排這次會議
Congresswoman, I asked LeAnn to have this meeting set up
是因為我有個大膽的提議
because I have a radical proposal,
我想當面跟你提出
and I wanted to make it in person.
道格已經跟我說了
Well, Doug has already filled me in.
我一般不會為任何人背書四年
Usually, I wouldn't endorse anyone four years out,
但這次  我樂意考慮
but in this case, I'm really open to it.
能讓民主黨人進入州長府邸就好
Anything to put a Democrat into the governor's mansion.
我跟議員女士說
I told the congresswoman that
用上她在達拉斯的政治力量
enlisting her political machinery in Dallas
是很關鍵的第一步
is a crucial first step.
所以我叫我女兒也一起來了
Which is why I asked my daughter to join us.
到時她已經接替了我的席位  你倆可以密切合作
She'll have my seat by then, and you two will work closely.
我對您十分敬重  安德伍德夫人
I have a great deal of respect for you, Mrs. Underwood.
我認為我們攜手可以成就輝煌
I think we can accomplish a lot together.
其實  議員女士
Well, actually, Congresswoman,
我認為如果不先當選公職
I've decided that the governorship is a big leap
直接做州長跨度太大
without holding any elected office first.
你在考慮下一輪競選參議員嗎
Are you thinking Senate next cycle?
不  我在考慮本輪競選你的選區
No, I'm thinking your district, this cycle.
那樣的話  您女兒就得等等
That would mean your daughter holds off,
等我競選州長時
and then I would throw my full weight behind her
會全力支持她接替我
to replace me when I run for governor.
我已經組織了團隊
I've already put together my team.
不  你還是能得到席位的  西莉婭
Oh, no, you would still get the seat, Celia.
我只是求你再等等
I'm just asking you to wait a little longer.
總統認為這個方案最好
And the president thinks this is the best plan.
你怎么沒說
Why didn't you tell me this?
-我并不知道  夫人  -他和我私下談的
- I wasn't aware, ma'am. - Well, he and I spoke privately about it.
西莉婭為了等我退休已經等了十年多
Celia has waited over a decade for me to retire.
該輪到她了
It's her time.
我理解
I understand.
所以等她接過了席位  我希望能給她
And that's why I want to put her in the best position to succeed
-最有利的地位  -你上次踏入
- when she takes office. - When was the last time
這個選區是什么時候了
you set foot in this district?
弗蘭西斯當選黨鞭的時候
When Francis was elected whip.
我們要怎么要求選民支持一個
So, how are we supposed to ask our people to support a woman
根本不了解他們的女人
that doesn't even know them?
不了解他們的生活  他們每日的掙扎
Their lives, their everyday struggles.
投機謀利
Carpetbagger.
還是白人
Who's white.
不僅是種族問題  安德伍德夫人
It goes deeper than race, Mrs. Underwood.
你在海蘭帕克長大  從小不缺吃穿
You grew up in Highland Park, never wanted for anything.
你無法體現我們的群體
You just don't reflect our community.
議員女士說得有道理
Congresswoman makes a good point.
我是想要個跳板
What I want is a stepping stone.
而你想聯邦資助一家計劃生育組織經營的
And what you want is federal funding for a breast cancer center
乳腺癌中心
run by Planned Parenthood.
如果共和黨控制了國會  這就無法實現
Something that a Republican-controlled Congress will never do.
尤其是在退伍軍人醫院
Especially in a VA hospital.
即便是民主黨控制國會時你也遭遇了阻力
You had resistance even when the Democrats controlled the House.
但國會議員  不管是共和黨還是民主黨
But there's not one congressperson, Republican or Democrat,
都不會拒絕跟第一夫人見面
that would refuse a meeting with the First Lady.
你說得對  安德伍德夫人
You're right, Mrs. Underwood.
我們沒能實現我們的一切目標
We haven't accomplished everything we set out to do.
但我的選民一直擁有的
But the one thing my constituents have always had...
是由自己人代表的驕傲
is the pride that they take in being represented by one of their own.
我不能剝奪這份驕傲
I refuse to rob them of that.
多謝您抽時間  議員女士
Thank you for your time, Congresswoman.
我們會重新考慮再聯系您  謝謝
We'll reassess our thinking and get back to you. Thank you.
你叫總統別插手
You tell the president to stay out of this.
或許您該直接跟他談
Maybe you should speak to him directly.
如果他肯支持我競選  我就跟他談
As soon as he's willing to support this race, I'll talk to him.
您在犯錯誤  安德伍德夫人
You're making a mistake, Mrs. Underwood.
白宮內部人士透露
A source within the White House tells us this,
第一夫人跟丈夫
that the First Lady traveled to Texas
大吵一架后飛去了德州
after some sort of a major argument with her husband.
第一夫人在德州
初選工作還是婚姻分歧
總統稱她去達拉斯
Well, the president has claimed that she went to Dallas
是為德州初選打基礎
to lay groundwork for the Texas primary.
但她三天前抵達后  卻不見舉辦任何
But there's no evidence of any campaign events or fundraisers
競選活動或籌款活動
since she arrived there three days ago,
也未曾公開露面
and she hasn't appeared publicly.
那么  莫妮卡  得問問你對此事的看法
So, Monica, gotta get your take on this.
如果真的出現了婚姻不和
Well, if there is marital discord,
安德伍德夫婦肯定不愿承認
the Underwoods certainly wouldn't want to admit it.
她去那邊籌備初選
Her being down there for the primary?
拜托  那完全可能是障眼法
Come on, that could be a smokescreen.
-胡安  -格雷琴  我們現實點
- Juan? - Well, come on, Gretchen. Let's be real.
這事不對勁啊
Something's rotten in the state of Denmark.
這時機簡直太糟了
I mean, the timing on this could not be worse.
別忘了  新罕布什爾初選就在明天
Don't forget, the New Hampshire primary is tomorrow.
總統從愛荷華州帶出來的好勢頭
So, whatever momentum the president had coming out of Iowa...
現在都像氣球泄氣一樣流逝了
Just like air going out of a popped balloon.
希瑟·鄧巴對此
Well, you know that Heather Dunbar
肯定有話說  我們看看吧
is gonna have something to say about this. Let's take a look.
希瑟·鄧巴
針對安德伍德婚姻傳言的回應
我不知道此事是真是假
I don't know whether this story is true or not,
但如果是  我希望總統和第一夫人
but if it is, I hope that the president and the First Lady
能調和矛盾
can work out their differences.
沒人希望看到一段婚姻出現問題
No one likes to see a marriage under strain.
個人而言  如果不是我了不起的家人
Personally, I wouldn't be able to carry on my campaign
我也沒法競選...
without the incredible...
知道是哪里走漏的消息嗎
Do we know where the leak came from?
我們在找特勤局和員工問話
We're talking to Secret Service and to staff now,
但是  先生  暫時還不知道
but no, sir, we don't know yet.
我這兒有一堆十磅重的剪報
I'm looking at a ten-pound stack of clippings,
這還只是過去一小時里出來的報道
and that's just what's been written in the past hour.
這是鄧巴干的  我知道是她搗的鬼
This is Dunbar. I know she's behind this.
先生  我可能有辦法了
Sir, I might have a solution.
我們能單獨談談嗎
May we speak privately for a moment?
好  賽斯  掛線
Yeah. Seth, hop off the line.
如果我們要改變策略  我覺得...
If we're gonna switch tactics, I think I should--
如果總統打算采取措施我會告訴你的
I'll fill you in if the president wants to move forward.
掛線  賽斯
Hop off, Seth.
在辯論中  我們都記得
During the debates, we all remember,
安德伍德攻擊夏普把孩子送去私立學校
Underwood went after Sharp for sending her kids to private...
白宮不睦
好了  說吧
All right, go ahead.
克萊爾的母親
Claire's mother.
她怎么了
What about her?
第一夫婦吵架  克萊爾·安德伍德走人
你五歲的時候我就告訴你
I told you when you were five years old
進屋一定要跟我打招呼
not to come in this house without saying hello to me.
我到時就去看過你  你當時睡了
I came by when I arrived. You were asleep.
那是兩天前了
That was two days ago.
我不知道你是不是想見我  母親
Well, I wasn't sure you wanted to see me, Mother.
好吧
Well...
既然我們要生活在一個屋檐下
as long as we're living under the same roof
-而且還被新聞車包圍  -那個很抱歉
- and besieged by news trucks-- - I apologize for all that.
是真的嗎
Is it true?
你是因為這個才來這兒嗎
Is that why you came down here?
不  我來是因為
No, I came down here because...
那個來訪的女人
That woman who visited...
-莉安·哈維  -我知道她是誰
- LeAnn Harvey. - Mmm-hmm, I know who she is.
她推銷候選人的時候經常打給我
She calls me all the time asking for money when she's...
問我要錢
peddling some candidate.
你是候選人嗎
Are you the candidate?
國會  30選區
Congress. 30th District.
這樣啊
I see.
你不贊成
You don't approve.
你總是自己做決定
Well, you've always made your choices
不管我怎么想
regardless of what I think.
他怎么想
What does he think?
他跟你談話了嗎  勸我別那么做
Has he spoken to you? To discourage me?
你爸爸葬禮那天之后他就再沒跟我說過話
He hasn't spoken to me since the day of your daddy's funeral.
你也一樣
Just like you haven't.
你當上第一夫人都不來通電話
Not even a phone call when you became First Lady--
如果你不希望我待在這兒  我可以另做安排
If you don't want me here, I can make other arrangements.
別傻了
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
這房子是我的也是你的
This house is as much yours as it is mine.
我把東西都罩上
I put covers on everything
否則女仆還得打掃我從不進的房間
because the maids were cleaning rooms I never set foot in.
但既然你來了
But now that you're here...
別動了
Just leave them.
我只需要一間臥室
I only need a bedroom.
好吧
Fine.
這房子對你來說就是個旅館
This house is just a hotel to you.
總統今天下午晚些時候會抵達達拉斯
The president will arrive in Dallas later this afternoon.
至于他此行的目的  我目前不能透露
As to the nature of his trip, I can't comment at this time
只能說他打算見第一夫人
other than to say he plans on seeing the First Lady.
-賽斯  -馬克
- Seth! - Mark.
他南下似乎讓他們婚姻出現問題的說法
His going down there would seem to lend legitimacy to claims
看起來更有依據了  不是嗎
that they're having marital issues, wouldn't it?
我們已經否認了那種說法
We've already denied those claims.
-賽斯  -莎拉
- Seth! - Sara.
報道爆出后  總統
Neither the president nor the First Lady
和第一夫人都未曾公開做過回應
have publicly responded since this story broke.
他們會回應嗎
Can we expect them to?
你所謂的報道  并非報道
What you're calling a story isn't a story.
只是個奪人眼球的標題
It's a flashy headline
幫你們在推特上漲粉
that gives you a bump in Twitter followers.
根本不值得對此做出回應
It doesn't warrant a response,
但如果總統或第一夫人決定回應
but if the president or First Lady chooses to make one,
肯定第一個告訴你
you'll be the first to know.
-賽斯  -謝謝大家
- Seth! - Thank you all very much.
-她離開多久了  -沒多久
- How long has she been gone? - Not long.
-去了莉安·哈維辦公室  -老天
- LeAnn Harvey's office. - Christ.
媒體沒跟著她吧
The press didn't follow her, did they?
沒有  他們走了條公用設施路
No. They took a utility road out.
沒有警察隨行
No police escort.
你倆要把問都不問一聲就跑來
Are you two gonna make a habit of showing up here
當成習慣嗎
without even the courtesy of asking?
我也希望不用來這兒
I wish I didn't have to be here,
但你女兒逼得我沒辦法
but your daughter's made it necessary.
她結婚時
You know, when she got married,
我以為過一兩年她肯定會醒悟
I was sure she would wake up in a year or two.
沒想到她用了30年
I had no idea it was gonna take her 30.
克萊爾是美國的第一夫人
Claire is the First Lady of the United States,
你還覺得她選錯了人
and you still think she made the wrong choice.
變成小報談資了
Reduced to tabloid gossip?
她跟住在你出身的那個拖車公園有什么區別
She might as well be living in that trailer park you come from.
是個桃子園
Well, it was a peach farm.
但你沒說錯  我還是白人垃圾
But you're right, I am still white trash.
我只不過恰好是個住在白宮的白人垃圾
I just happen to be white trash that lives in the White House.
就算當上總統  還是那么粗俗
Not even being president could give you any class.
我告訴你接下來會怎么樣吧  伊麗莎白
Well, let me tell you what's about to happen, Elizabeth.
我不會站在交火的總統
I am not going to put myself in the crossfire
和第一夫人之間
between a president and First Lady.
我來應付弗蘭西斯
Oh, I'll handle Francis.
你說他同意的
You said he was on board.
我會讓他同意的
And I'll make sure he is.
重點是  你誤導了我  安德伍德夫人
The point is you misled me, Mrs. Underwood.
你想要什么  莉安  錢嗎
What is it you want, LeAnn? Is it money?
還是想要更多  真正有所成就
Or do you want more, to make a real mark?
我不用選  我可以兼得
I don't have to choose. I can have both.
如果你想青史留名  你就得離開德州
Well, if you wanna make history, you need to get out of Texas.
我拒絕過不少華府的工作
I've turned down plenty of jobs in D.C.
一年應付15位客戶
Juggling 15 clients a year.
但我想要你接下來15年的時間
But I want the next 15 years of your life.
德州只是我們的起點
Texas is just where we begin.
看來你到底是沒聽到
It seems you didn't hear me after all.
我不向威脅低頭
I don't respond to threats.
你在跟總統說話
You're speaking to the president.
是的  我認得出他的聲音
Yes, I recognize his voice.
請讓我單獨跟我妻子談談
I'd like to talk to my wife alone, please.
她留下  你想跟我說什么就說吧
She stays. Tell me what you need to tell me.
道格
Doug.
她已經病了三年了
She's been sick for three years.
放療  化療  都做了
Radiation, chemotherapy, the works.
但你不知道  是嗎
But you didn't know, did you?
你不能把我母親拉到鏡頭前
You're not dragging my mother in front of the cameras.
只有你一人  你要說你是為此才南下
Just you, and you're going to say that that's why you're down here.
這是家事  弗蘭西斯
This is a family matter, Francis.
這事必須做  克萊爾  我們得把傳言止住
This has to be done, Claire. We have to kill this story.
他說得對
He's right.
我要知道你不會給我的競選搗亂
I need to know you won't meddle with my campaign.
國情咨文就在兩周之后
The State of the Union is in two weeks.
你到場  我就不再阻撓你
You show up for that, then I'll leave you alone.
我們趕緊了事吧
Let's get this over with.
克萊爾最初來到達拉斯時
When Claire first came down here to Dallas...
我們說是為德州的初選打基礎
we said it was to lay the groundwork for the Texas primary.
這也算是事實
And that was partially true.
但我們沒說的  是一些本想保密的私事
What we left out was something that we hoped to keep private.
但鑒于這幾天來關于我們婚姻狀況的
But in light of false stories over the last number of days
漫天謠傳
about the state of our marriage,
我們現在認為只能說出這一不幸的消息
we now feel it's important to share this unfortunate news.
克萊爾
Claire.
這三年來
For the past three years,
我母親一直在與間歇性淋巴癌做抗爭
my mother has been suffering from intermittent lymphoma.
起初  她在與病魔的抗爭中取得了勝利
Initially, she had some success battling her illness,
但這幾個月  疾病復發而且非常嚴重
but it's come back full force the last several months.
所以  我來這兒陪她
So, I came down here to spend time with her
進行進一步的治療
while she undergoes further treatment.
看在我母親尊嚴和健康的分上
And we ask just for the sake of my mother's dignity...
我們請求大家尊重她的隱私
and well-being that you respect her privacy.
謝謝
Thank you.
我明天將繼續我的競選
I will be resuming my campaign tomorrow
克萊爾  當然了  將留在這里
and Claire will, of course, be staying here.
我還要說
And let me just add...
克萊爾的母親有這樣孝順的女兒是莫大的福氣
Claire's mother is blessed to have such a loving daughter.
我有如此體貼  善良的妻子也是三生有幸
And I am blessed to have such a thoughtful and caring wife.
謝謝大家
Thank you all very much.
平平常常  但也足矣了
Nothing fancy, but it'll do the job.
你正式是約翰·卡萊爾了
You're officially John Carlyle now.
駕照有意弄了個過期的  你得乘大巴上班
Driver's license is expired on purpose. You take the bus to work.
把一切都背下來  地址  生日  社保號
Memorize everything, address, birthday, social.
還有個人經歷  也要熟練背下來
There's a personal history in there for you to know by heart, too.
-"飛馬租車行"  -對
- "Pegasus Car Rentals"? - Yeah.
你洗租車  明天開始
You wash rentals. It starts tomorrow.
保持低調
Keep a low profile.
別表現出異常
Don't be weird about it,
別到處交朋友
don't go out of your way to make friends.
如果...
What if there's...
出什么事了呢
If something's wrong?
固話直接接到我們本地辦公室
Landline goes directly to our local office.
出門在外  用旁邊那部手機
Away from home, use the cell phone next to it.
-還有什么  -你有基本的有線臺
- What else? - You have basic cable.
當然了  沒有網
No Internet, obviously.
百葉窗拉好  門鎖好
Keep the blinds drawn and the doors locked.
就這樣了
That's it.
本周晚些時候我再來找你
I'll check in with you later this week.
我們不僅在新罕布什爾獲勝
Now, we didn't just win a plurality here in New Hampshire.
而且差距懸殊
We won a majority.
知道這意味著什么嗎
Now, you know what that tells me?
看來等票全數完  鄧巴能領先
It's looking like Dunbar's got it by 11 or 12 points
11到12個百分點
by the time everything's counted.
已經報上來幾個區了
How many precincts have reported?
兩分鐘前是83%
As of two minutes ago, 83%.
賽斯起草了講話  等我們落地后用
Seth drafted a speech for when we land.
一般來說  鄧巴會等你先發表講話
Normally, Dunbar would wait to give her speech until after yours,
但既然我們在飛機上
but since we're on the plane--
-給她打電話  我讓她  -好  先生
- Get her on the phone and I'll concede. - Yes, sir.
看那個乳臭未干的小白臉
Look at that snot-nosed pretty-boy.
他肯定剛學會刮胡子
I'll bet he just learned how to shave.
接鄧巴
Get me Dunbar.
-女士  我真覺得...  -開門
- Ma'am, I really think-- - Open it.
她想一個人待著
She wants to be left alone.
打開門
Unlock the door.
你走
I want you to go!
母親
Mother...
你為什么沒告訴我
why didn't you tell me?
因為不關你的事
Because it was none of your business.
-聽我說  -不  別費口舌了
- Just listen to me. - No, don't even bother.
我明白你為什么那么做
I understand why you did what you did.
但也還是一樣傷人
But that doesn't make it any less hurtful.
那是為了我還是為了你自己
Is that for me or for yourself?
克萊爾
Claire.
過來
Come here.
你比他強大
You're stronger than he is.
但你得讓他知道你的厲害
But you gotta put him in his place.
■
與普選不同  美國各州的初選投票時間分散  前后長達數月
有時同一州民主黨與共和黨投票的時間也不同
如2016年美國總統大選  從2月1日的愛荷華州初選
到6月14日的首都華盛頓投票  兩黨初選要持續四個半月的時間
初選開局階段主要包括愛荷華州  新罕布什爾州  南卡羅來納州
以及內華達州這四州的選舉  時間上先后有別
因此先舉行初選的幾個州的選舉結果就非常重要
在最初的幾個州獲勝  不僅能助長候選人的氣勢  贏得尚未投票的選民的認可
還能獲得媒體的關注  令黨內大小金主慷慨捐款
2016年的總統選舉中  愛荷華州選舉結果揭曉當晚
兩黨便各有一名候選人因成績不佳而宣布退選
前三個州初選結束后  兩黨共有八名候選人宣布退出
包括曾很受看好的前總統小布什的弟弟  杰布·布什
■
新罕布什爾是第二個舉行初選的州
選舉結果舉足輕重  而該州面積小  人口少
因此歷史上總統候選人在新罕布什爾的選舉活動
多以小型集會為主
以便選民對各個候選人的立場進行深入透徹的了解
有時候候選人甚至需要挨家挨戶敲門拉票
所以這里的競選方式被媒體稱為  "零售式競選"